let savollar30 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "above",
        answer: "A. ustida",
        options: [
            "A. ustida",
            "B. ostida",
            "C. yonida",
            "D. orqasida"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "ahead",
        answer: "B. oldinda",
        options: [
            "A. orqasida",
            "B. oldinda",
            "C. yonida",
            "D. o'rtasida"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "amount",
        answer: "C. miqdor",
        options: [
            "A. vazn",
            "B. uzunlik",
            "C. miqdor",
            "D. maydon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "belief",
        answer: "D. ishonch",
        options: [
            "A. shubha",
            "B. qo'rquv",
            "C. umid",
            "D. ishonch"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "center",
        answer: "A. markaz",
        options: [
            "A. markaz",
            "B. chet",
            "C. burchak",
            "D. tomon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "common",
        answer: "B. odatiy",
        options: [
            "A. kamdan-kam",
            "B. odatiy",
            "C. noyob",
            "D. g'alati"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "cost",
        answer: "D. narx turmoq",
        options: [
            "A. tejash",
            "B. topish",
            "C. yig'ish",
            "D. narx turmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "demonstrate",
        answer: "A. namoyish qilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. namoyish qilmoq",
            "B. yashirmoq",
            "C. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "D. unutmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "different",
        answer: "C. turli xil",
        options: [
            "A. bir xil",
            "B. o'xshash",
            "C. turli xil",
            "D. odatiy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "evidence",
        answer: "D. dalil",
        options: [
            "A. taxmin",
            "B. nazariya",
            "C. spekulyatsiya",
            "D. dalil"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "honesty",
        answer: "A. to'g'riso'zlik",
        options: [
            "A. to'g'riso'zlik",
            "B. yolg'on",
            "C. firibgarlik",
            "D. aldov"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "idiom",
        answer: "C. idioma",
        options: [
            "A. so'z",
            "B. gap",
            "C. idioma",
            "D. kitob"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "independent",
        answer: "B. mustaqil",
        options: [
            "A. qaram",
            "B. mustaqil",
            "C. nazorat qilinadigan",
            "D. tutqun"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "inside",
        answer: "D. ichi",
        options: [
            "A. tashqarisida",
            "B. yuqorisida",
            "C. pastida",
            "D. ichi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "master",
        answer: "A. usta",
        options: [
            "A. usta",
            "B. shogird",
            "C. boshlovchi",
            "D. talaba"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "memory",
        answer: "B. xotira",
        options: [
            "A. unutish",
            "B. xotira",
            "C. hozirgi",
            "D. kelajak"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "proper",
        answer: "C. o'rinli",
        options: [
            "A. noo'rinli",
            "B. noo'rin",
            "C. to'g'ri",
            "D. odatiy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "scan",
        answer: "A. qarab chiqmoq",
        options: [
            "A. qarab chiqmoq",
            "B. ko'rmaslik",
            "C. e'tiborsiz qoldirish",
            "D. o'chirish"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "section",
        answer: "B. bo'lim",
        options: [
            "A. butunlik",
            "B. bo'lim",
            "C. qism",
            "D. detal"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "surface",
        answer: "D. sirt",
        options: [
            "A. chuqurlik",
            "B. ichki qism",
            "C. chet",
            "D. sirt"
        ]
    }
];
